

# SHAH

# UI / UX DESIGNER

Graphic Design

UI / UX Design

Front-End Dev

2D Animation

#### About me:

Experienced graphic designer with 11 years in the industry. Keenly interested in front-end development and UI / UX design. Known for a strong work ethic, passion for learning, and a drive for excellence in competitive environments.

Name Muhammad Shahril Fadzlyn

Bin Baharin

Language Malay • Native

English • Basic

#### CONTACT

Mobile 016 - 9191 002

E-mail shahrilfadzlyn@gmail.com

Website shahrilfadzlyn.github.io/portfolio

Address 11, Jalan Wangsa 1/3,

Taman Wangsa Permai, 52200, Kuala Lumpur

#### REFERENCE

Name Mr. S S Loong

Position Manager of Prepress Dept.

Mobile 017 - 692 1538

Address UPA PRESS SDN. BHD.

Lot 8228, Batu 6½, Jalan Kuchai Lama 58200 Kuala Lumpur.



# WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

**Graphic Designer** (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd
Creative Designer (Freelance)

2021 - 2022 Jawi Streetwear

Founder / Product Designer (Self-employed)

2017 - 2018 SF Motion Studio

Founder / 2D Animator (Self-employed)

2014 - 2017 UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

**Graphic Designer** (Permanent)

2013 - 2014 iProduksi

**2D Animator** (Freelance)

**FNF** Printing

**Graphic Designer** (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept

Wedding Photographer (Self-employed)

2011 DotPerInchStudio

**Graphic Designer** (Internship)



## **EDUCATION**

2011 - 2013 Ba (hons) Media Practice with Animation

**Second Class Honours (Upper Division)** 

University of the West of England, United Kingdom

2008 - 2011 Diploma in Digital Media Design

CGPA 3.67

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

2006 - 2007 SPM; 1A, 3B, 2C, 2D, 1E

SMK Sri Tasik, Kuala Lumpur



# **ACHIEVEMENT**

2015 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2014 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2010 **1st Place winner**, Graphic Design Technology,

Malaysia Skills Competition, 19th

Best Artwork Award, Digital Media, 5th Semester

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

**All Rounder Best Artwork Award** Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau



#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### **Adobe Suite**

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Flash/Animate, After Effects, Premiere & Audition

Microsoft Office Suite
Word, Excel & Powerpoint

#### Coding

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

#### Other Software/App

Figma, VSCode, Canva, Capcut, ChatGPT 4



# MUHAMMAD SHAHRIL FADZLYN BIN BAHARIN

UI / UX DESIGNER

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Graphic Designer**

UPA Press Sdn. Bhd. 2017 - Present (Freelance) 2014 - 2017 (Permanent)

- Designed table calendars and diaries for domestic and international clients, adhering to their brand guidelines.
- Maintained clear communication with clients throughout the design process, finalizing artwork to their satisfaction.
- Utilized laser cutting and prepress printing machines to create color proofs and mock-up samples.
- Collaborated effectively with sales, supervisors, and production to ensure project success.
- Contributed to the development of new products through participation in the R&D team.
- Photographed product lines to create visually appealing marketing materials.
- · Mentored junior graphic designers.
- Designed a modern and user-friendly company website using Figma.

#### Creative Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd. | 2021 - Present

- Developed the company's branding (logo, business card, etc).
- Contributed to UI/UX design for the company website & app.
- Conceptualized and produced a video ad to promote the company's app.
- Designed the company's marketing materials.

#### Founder/ Product Designer (Self-employed)

Jawi Streetwear | 2021 - 2022

- Developed brand identity (logo, marketing materials, etc).
- Conducted product research, designed & launched website & social media.
- Established relationships with key suppliers for cost-effective delivery.
- Generated engaging content (photos, videos) for multi-channel marketing.
- Developed customer relationships & drove sales.

#### **2D Animator** (Self-employed)

SF Motion Studio | 2017 - 2018

- Created engaging 2D animation content for Facebook and YouTube.
- Freelanced as a 2D animator and graphic designer on Fiverr, serving international clients.

#### 2D Animator (Freelance)

iProduksi | 2013 - 2014

 Developed concept art and produced animated projects, including a music video for a TV3 campaign and a cartoon series pilot episode.

#### Wedding photographer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept | 2013 - 2014

Captured wedding ceremony moments through professional photography.

#### **Graphic Designer** (Self-employed)

FNF Printing | 2013 - 2014

- Established our company's brand identity (logo, business cards, etc.).
- Designed marketing materials for clients, including bunting, banners, business cards, and T-shirts.